craft.co 2019-03-26

# Privacy and Security Policy - Craft

Date Last Revised:  **May 17, 2018**

 _Craft is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information about our users._

This Privacy & Security Policy explains how we protect personal information provided through our website [www.Craft.co](http://www.craft.co/) (the "Site") and how we use that information in connection with our service offered through the Site (the “Service”). “Personal information” for purposes of this Policy means information that identifies you.

#### 1\. We care about the privacy of Craft users. 

Simply put, we do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time. Craft uses and discloses your personal information only as follows:

  * to fulfill your requests for certain products and services;
  * to analyze site usage and improve the Service;
  * to deliver to you any notices and communications relevant to your use of the Service;
  * for research, planning, troubleshooting problems;
  * to third-party contractors that provide services (e.g. email notifications) to Craft and are bound by these same privacy restrictions;
  * to enforce Craft’s Terms of Use; and
  * as otherwise set forth in this Privacy and Security Policy.

Craft may make anonymous or aggregate personal information and disclose such data only in a non-personally identifiable manner to:

  * Users of the Service for purposes of comparison to the broader community;
  * Organizations approved by Craft that conduct research into career management and development; and
  * Advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes.

Such information does not identify you individually. Access to any personal information you provide is strictly restricted and used in accordance with specific internal procedures and safeguard governing access, in order to operate, develop or improve the Service.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16. If you are under 16, please do not attempt to register for the Service or send any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 16 may have provided us personal information, please contact us at security@craft.co.   

#### 2\. Online session information and use is only used to improve your experience.

When you visit Craft.co, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Site. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality.

“Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Craft may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you. Craft may gather information about you through cookie technology. For example, Craft may assign a cookie to you, to limit the amount of times you see a particular notification. Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer. If you choose to eliminate cookies, the full functionality of the Service may be impaired for you.

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us analyze visitor activity on Craft.co. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for Craft. We do not share any personal information about our customers with these third party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information on our behalf. Our third party service providers are required to comply fully with this Privacy and Security Policy. One of these services is Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Service. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). You may also download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add on, available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

#### 3\. Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Craft reserves the right (and you authorize Craft) to share or disclose your personal information when Craft determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate:

  * To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the Craft.co Terms of Use;
  * To prevent prohibited or illegal activities; or
  * When required by any applicable law, rule regulation, subpoena or other legal process.

#### 4\. Your data may be transferred upon change of control but only in accordance with this Policy.

Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization or other change of control. If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. If so, you will be asked if you'd like to stop receiving promotional information following any change of control.

#### 5\. You can transport or delete your data.

Your data is yours. You can remove it anytime you want. When you request us to delete your account for the Service, your data will be permanently expunged from our primary production servers and further access to your account will not be possible. We will also promptly disconnect any connection we had established to your Account Information and delete all account credentials. However, portions of your data, consisting of aggregate data derived from your Account Information, may remain on our production servers indefinitely. Your data may also remain on a backup server or media. Craft keeps these backups to ensure our continued ability to provide the Service to you in the event of malfunction or damage to our primary production servers. We also reserve the right to use any aggregated or anonymous data derived from or incorporating your personal information.

#### 6\. Your data is secure.

We use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Craft.co accounts and systems from unauthorized access.

When you register for the Service, Craft requires a password from you for your privacy and security. Craft transmits information such as your Registration Information for Craft.co or Account Credentials securely.

Our servers are in a secure facility. Access requires multiple levels of authentication, including biometrics recognition procedures. Security personnel monitor the system 7 days a week, 24 hours a day.

Our databases are protected from general employee access both physically and logically. We encrypt your Service password so that your password cannot be recovered, even by us. All backup drives and tapes also are encrypted.

#### 7\. Our service ensures secure communications with encryption

From the time you submit your Login ID and Password, these communications between your computer and Craft.co are encrypted. This enables client and server applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering and message forgery.

#### 8\. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Login ID and Password.

We maintain strict rules to help prevent others from guessing your password. Your password must be 6-16 characters in length. You are responsible for maintaining the security of your Login ID and Password. You may not provide these credentials to any third party. If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at [security@craft.co](mailto:security@craft.co) and you should change your password immediately via the Service. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through Registration Information they have obtained from you or through a violation by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the MyCareerPal.co Terms of Use.

If you have a security related concern, please contact us at [security@craft.co](mailto:security@craft.co). We will work closely with you to ensure a rapid and personal response to your concerns.

#### 9\. We post updates on our website whenever there is a change to our Privacy and Security Policy.

We update this Privacy & Security Policy periodically. The date last revised appears at the top of the Policy. Changes take effect immediately upon posting.

#### 10\. Contact us if you have any questions or concerns.

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy and Security Policy or any other privacy or security concern, please send us an e-mail at [security@craft.co](mailto:security@craft.co).
